Guide to the Franklin Bowditch Dexter Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Files on Alumni, Circa 1701-1912; Series I; 9' (22 boxes)
  - White, Roger Sherman. 1859
  - White, Roger Sherman. 1899
  - White, Stephen. 1736
  - White, Thomas Howell. 1860
  - Whitehead, Amos. 1804 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Whiting, Francis. 1829 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Whiting, John. 1726 (Box 18, Folder 219)
    See also: Welles, Gideon, box 18, folder 215.
  - Whiting, John. 1774 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Whiting, Samuel. 1765 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Whitmore, Matthew Noyes. 1854 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Whitney, Ebeny. 1854 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Whitney, Henry Otis. 1866 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Whitney, Joseph Ernest. 1882 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Whitney, William Dwight. 1867h (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Whiton, James Morris. 1853, 1856h (Box 18, Folder 220)
  - Whiton, John Milton. 1805 (Box 18, Folder 220)
    See also: Whiton, James Morris, box 18, folder 220.
  - Whittelsey General Folder
    See: box 21, folder 259.
  - Whittelsey, Charles Chauncey. 1838
    See: Whittelsey General Folder, box 21, folder 259.
  - Whittelsey, Charles Henry. 1853 (Box 18, Folder 220)
  - Whittelsey, Chauncey. 1738 (Box 18, Folder 220)
    See also: Whittelsey General Folder, box 21, folder 259.
    See also: Van Deursen, William, box 18, folder 209.
  - Whittelsey, Chauncey. 1764
    See: Whittelsey, Chauncey (1738), box 18, folder 220.
  - Whittelsey, Chauncey. 1800
  - Whittelsey, Chauncey. 1820
  - Whittelsey, Ira. 1843
  - Whittelsey, John. 1791
  - Whittelsey, Newton. 1773
  - Whittelsey, Samuel. 1705
  - Whittelsey, Samuel. 1729
  - Whittelsey, Samuel. 1764
  - Whittelsey, Samuel. 1779
  - Whittelsey, Samuel. 1803
  - Whittelsey, Samuel Goodrich. 1834
  - Whittlesey, Charles Barnes. 1843m (Box 18, Folder 220)
  - Whittlesey, Eliphalet. 1842
  - Whittlesey, Elisha. 1779
  - Whittlesey, Elisha. 1811
  - Whittlesey, Frederick. 1818
  - Whittlesey, Frederick. 1822
  - Whittlesey, Joseph. 1825
  - Whittlesey, Luman. 1816 (Box 18, Folder 220)
  - Whittlesey, Martin Kellogg. 1844
  - Whittlesey, Roger. 1787
  - Whittlesey, Thomas Turner. 1817 (Box 18, Folder 220)
  - Whittlesey, William. 1827
  - Whittelsey, William Augustus. 1816
  - Wick, John. 1722 (Box 18, Folder 220)
  - Wickes, Simon Alexander. 1827 (Box 18, Folder 220)
  - Wickes, Thomas. 1834 (Box 18, Folder 220)
  - Wickes, Thomas Scudder. 1814
  - Wickham, Edmund Fanning. 1815
  - Wickham, Joseph Dresser. 1815 (Box 18, Folder 221)
    See also: Wickham, Thomas, box 18, folder 221.
  - Wickham, Thomas. 1754 (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Wickham, William. 1753 (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Wight, John. 1823 (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Wightman, Stillman King. 1825 (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Wilbur, Nathan Fox. 1845 (Box 18, Folder 221)
    See also: Grant, John, box 8, folder 78.
  - Wilbur, Thomas. 1824m (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Wilcox, James A. 1850 non-graduate (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Wilcox, Justus Denslow. 1855h (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Wilcoxson, Julius Denslow. 1812 (Box 18, Folder 221)
    See also: Wilcoxson, Martin Van Buren, box 21, folder 259.
  - Wilcoxson, Levi Dibble. 1839 (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Wilcoxson, Martin Van Buren. 1847
  - Wilder, Horace. 1823 (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Wilder, Josiah. 1767 (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Wilkins, Edmund. 1817 (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Wilkins, Gouverneur Morris. 1818 (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Wilkins, Gouverneur Morris. 1847 (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Wilkins, John Limbrey. 1820 (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Wilkins, William Webb. 1822 (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Willard, Horace Kemper. 1829m (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Willard, Joseph. 1714 (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Willard, Samuel George. 1846 (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Willcox, Wallace Cornwell. 1847 (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Willcox, William Henry. 1870h (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Willets, Andrew Jackson. 1855 (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Williams General Folder
  - Williams Alpheus Starkey. 1831 (Box 19, Folder 223)
  - Williams, Chester. 1735
  - Williams, Comfort. 1808
  - Williams, Dillon. 1836 (Box 19, Folder 223)
  - Williams, Ebenezer. 1773
  - Williams, Edward. 1730 (Box 19, Folder 223)
  - Williams, Eliphalet. 1743 (Box 19, Folder 223)
  - Williams, Elisha. 1735 (Box 19, Folder 223)
    See also: Williams, Elisha Scott, box 19, folder 223.
  - Williams, Elisha. 1767 (Box 19, Folder 223)
  - Williams, Elisha Scott. 1775 (Box 19, Folder 223)
  - Williams, Ezekiel. 1785
  - Williams, Francke. 1840m (Box 19, Folder 223)
  - Williams, Francke Sherman. 1869 (Box 19, Folder 223)
  - Williams, Israel. 1762
  - Williams, John. 1781
  - Williams, John. 1822
  - Williams, John Chester. 1765
  - Williams, John Stoddard. 1827
  - Williams, Jonathan. 1722
  - Williams, Jonathan Law. 1777
  - Williams, Joseph. 1798 (Box 19, Folder 224)
  - Williams, Joshua. 1780
  - Williams, Joshua. 1805
  - Williams, Nathan. 1755
  - Williams, Nathan. 1782
  - Williams, Nehemiah. 1769h
  - Williams, Oliver Ellsworth. 1816 (Box 19, Folder 224)
  - Williams, Orin Merwin. 1869 (Box 19, Folder 224)
  - Williams, Othniel. 1810 (Box 19, Folder 224)
  - Williams, Richard. 1802
  - Williams, Richard Salter. 1826
  - Williams, Robert Edwards. 1871 (Box 19, Folder 224)
  - Williams, Samuel. 1735
  - Williams, Samuel. 1786
  - Williams, Samuel Porter. 1796
  - Williams, Samuel William. 1772
  - Williams, Sidney Phoenix. 1829
  - Williams, Solomon. 1743 (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Williams, Solomon. 1770
  - Williams, Solomon. 1792
  - Williams, Stephen. 1741
  - Williams, Stephen. 1783
  - Williams, Stephen Clay. 1825 (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Williams, Thomas. 1748 (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Williams, Thomas. 1756
  - Williams, Thomas. ex-1783
  - Williams, Thomas Barnard. 1800 (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Williams, Thomas Scott. 1794
  - Williams, Thomas Scott. 1838
    See: Williams, Robert Edwards, box 19, folder 224.
  - Williams, Timothy. 1785
  - Williams, Warham. 1745
  - Williams, William. 1739
  - William, William. 1753h (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Williams, William. 1754
  - Williams, William Augustus. 1780
  - Williams, William Chauncey. 1842h
    See: Williams, William Cook, box 19, folder 225.
  - Williams, William Cook. 1850m (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Williams, William Frederic. 1840h (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Williams, William Perkins. 1839
  - Williams, William Trumbull. 1795
  - Williamson, Lewis Pugh. 1821
  - Willis, Nathaniel Parker. 1827
    See: Crane, Eliezer, box 5, folder 46.
  - Willis, Zephaniah. 1789h (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Williston, David Howe. 1787 (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Williston, John Payson. 1820
  - Williston, Noah. 1757
  - Willson, James Renwick. 1815h (Box 19, Folder 226)
  - Willson, Robert Newton. 1860 (Box 19, Folder 226)
  - Wilson, James Albert. 1889l (Box 19, Folder 226)
  - Wilson, John. 1847 (Box 19, Folder 226)
  - Wilson, William Thomas. 1855 (Box 19, Folder 226)
  - Winchester, George. 1816
  - Wing, Matthew Gregory. 1847 (Box 19, Folder 227)
  - Winship, James. 1847l (Box 19, Folder 227)
  - Winslow, Gordon. 1830 non-graduate (Box 19, Folder 227)
  - Winslow, Shadrach. 1771 (Box 19, Folder 227)
  - Winter, Enoch Terry. 1845m
    See: Van Rensselaer, Jeremiah, box 18, folder 209.
  - Winthrop, Edward. 1831 (Box 19, Folder 227)
    See also: Dwight, Timothy (1769), box 6, folder 58.
  - Winthrop, Francis Bayard. 1804
    See: Winthrop, Edward, box 19, folder 227.
    See: Winthrop, William Henry, box 19, folder 227.
  - Winthrop, William Henry. 1809 (Box 19, Folder 227)
  - Wiswall, Henry Trowbridge. 1847 (Box 19, Folder 227)
  - Withington, Leonard. 1814 (Box 19, Folder 227)
  - Witmer; Theodore Burg. 1840 (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Witter, Dexter. 1824 (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Witter, John. 1812 (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Wolcott, Edward Oliver. 1870 (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Wolcott, Herbert Walter. 1884
    See: Wolcott, Edward Oliver, box 19, folder 228.
  - Wolcott, Samuel. 1833
  - Wolcott, William. 1828 (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Wood, Arthur Burr. 1859 (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Wood, Joseph. 1801 (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Wood, Spencer. 1818 (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Wood, Theophilus Emmons. 1826m (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Wood, William Lamont. 1854h (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Wood, William Platt. 1872 (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Woodbridge, Diodate. 1736 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Woodbridge, Dudley. 1734 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Woodbridge, Henry Hopkins. 1823 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Woodbridge, John. 1726 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Woodbridge, Joshua Lamb. 1773
  - Woodbridge, Samuel. 1763 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Woodbridge, Timothy. [1706] (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Woodbridge, Timothy. 1765 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Woodbridge, William. 1780 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Woodbridge, William Channing. 1811 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Woodbridge, William Reed. 1855
  - Woodford, John Beach. 1839 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Woodford, Oswald Langdon. 1850 (Box 19, Folder 231)
    See also: Kellogg, Ebenezer, box 10, folder 108.
  - Woodhull, Caleb Smith. 1812 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Woodhull, George Lee. 1862 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Woodruff, Curtiss. 1838 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Woodruff, Ephraim Treadwell. 1797 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Woodruff, Ezekiel. 1779 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Woodruff, Gideon. 1785 (Box 19, Folder 231)
    See also: Woodruff, William, box 19, folder 231.
  - Woodruff, Samuel. 1782
  - Woodruff, Simeon. 1809 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Woodruff, William. 1826m (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Woods, John. 1755 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Woodward, Ashbel. 1855h
  - Woodward, Rufus. 1816 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Woodward, William Bassett. 1892p (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Woodworth, John. 1788
    See: Ely, John, box 20, folder 241.
  - Woolsey, Benjamin. 1709 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Woolsey, Benjamin. 1744 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Woolsey, Theodore Dwight. 1820
  - Wooster, Benjamin. 1790 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Wooster, David. 1738
  - Wooster, Joseph Lucius. 1781 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Wooster, Thomas. 1768 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Wootton, Henry Edgar. 1856 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Worcester, Joseph Emerson. 1811 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Worman, George Hunter. 1861 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Worrall, John Hunter. 1856 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Wortabet, John. 1853h (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Wright, Amos. 1832m (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Wright, Aron. 1836m (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Wright, Caleb. 1849h (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Wright, Charles. 1835 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Wright, Clark. 1881p (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Wright, David. 1777 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Wright, Ebenezer. 1724 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Wright, James Lockwood. 1832 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Wright, Joseph. 1804 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Wright, William. 1774 (Box 19, Folder 233)
    See also: Wright, David, box 19, folder 233.
  - Wyers, Frederick Augustus. 1872 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Wynkoop, Augustus. 1831 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Yale, Thomas. 1765 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Yancey, Antonio Poma. 1847 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Yardley, Henry Albert. 1855 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Youle, Joseph. 1815 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Young, David. 1798 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Young, Ebenezer. 1806 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Young, Francis James. 1866m
    See:Welch, William Wickham, box 18, folder 214.
  - Young, Guilford Dudley. 1822 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Youngs, David. 1741 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Youngs, Thomas. 1741 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Unidentified individuals, A-Z (Box 19, Folder 235)
  - Oversize
    General note
    See also: box 21, folder 259
    - Acker, Joel Milton. 1836 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Austin, Robert John Locke. 1822h (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Babcock, Joshua. 1724 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Baldwin, Burr. 1809 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Baldwin, James William. 1842 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Barnes, William. 1839 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Beach, John. 1721 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Beardsley, Lucius Nichols. 1838m (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Belden, Lemuel Whittlesey. 1821 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Bibbins, William Burr. 1845 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Bidwell, Barnabas. 1785 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Bissell, Hezekiah Woodbridge. 1793 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Botsford, Amos. 1763 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - Brown, Daniel. 1783 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - Brown, William. 1784 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - Bryant, William. 1747 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - Bulkley, Chauncey. 1817 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - Bulkley, Henry Daggett. 1821 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - Butts, Asa. 1822 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - Camp, Ichabod. 1743 (Box 20, Folder 238)
    - Carr, Wilson Cary Nicholas. 1846 (Box 20, Folder 238)
    - Chaulkins, John. 1788 (Box 20, Folder 238)
    - Chedsey, Nathan Augustus. 1848 (Box 20, Folder 238)
    - Clark, Gamaliel. 17341 (Box 20, Folder 238)
    - Clarke, Richard. 1762 (Box 20, Folder 239)
    - Clayton, John Middleton. 1815 (Box 20, Folder 239)
    - Collins, Levi. 1802 (Box 20, Folder 239)
    - Colton, Benjamin. 1710 (Box 20, Folder 239)
    - Colton, Simeon. 1806 (Box 20, Folder 239)
    - Cooke, Justus. 1779 (Box 20, Folder 239)
    - Cowles, David Smith. 1847h (Box 20, Folder 239)
    - Crane, John. 1813 (Box 20, Folder 240)
    - Crane, Matthias. 1747 (Box 20, Folder 240)
    - Cunningham, John Moffat. 1876p (Box 20, Folder 240)
    - Curtis, Holbrook. 1807 (Box 20, Folder 240)
    - Curtiss, Sheldon Clark. 1807 (Box 20, Folder 240)
    - Davis, James. 1815 (Box 20, Folder 240)
    - Day, Benjamin. 1768 (Box 20, Folder 240)
    - Dean, Richard Crain. 1853h (Box 20, Folder 240)
    - Dibble, John. 1758 (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - Dutton, Matthew Rice. 1808 (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - Duvillard, John Antoine. 1854p (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - Edwards, Jonathan. 1720 (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - Elliot, Harvey. 1805 (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - Ely, John. 1786 (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - Evans, Gurdon. 1850h (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Faulkner, Samuel Dorr. 1859 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Fenn, Benjamin. 1725 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Field, Seth. 1732 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Fitch, George. 1801 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Flagg, Levi Wells. 1839 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Fowler, John Douglass. 1813 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Fowler, William. 1860 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Gould., Horace Bunch. 1832 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Gould, William Tracy. 1816 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Grammer, John. 1817 (Box 20, Folder 243)
    - Guilford, Nathan. 1812 (Box 20, Folder 243)
    - Gunn, Frederick. 1810 (Box 20, Folder 243)
    - Harrison, Benjamin Franklin. 1836m (Box 20, Folder 243)
    - Hasbrouck, Abraham Bruyn. 1810 (Box 20, Folder 243)
    - Hathaway, Shadrach. 1738 (Box 20, Folder 244)
    - Hebard, Daniel. 1860 (Box 20, Folder 244)
    - Herrick, Edward. 1796 (Box 20, Folder 244)
    - Hewitt, Nathaniel. 1808 (Box 20, Folder 244)
    - Hickok, Horatio. 1798 (Box 20, Folder 244)
    - Hinckley, Edward Strong. 1859 (Box 20, Folder 244)
    - Hoffman, George Brice. 1828 (Box 20, Folder 245)
    - Holbrook, Samuel. 1801 (Box 20, Folder 245)
    - Hopkins, Charles. 1855 (Box 20, Folder 245)
    - Hotchkiss, Caleb. 1766 (Box 20, Folder 245)
    - Hotchkiss, Gabriel. 1774 (Box 20, Folder 245)
    - Hunt, Isaac Shafer. 1847m (Box 20, Folder 245)
    - Huntting, James Murdock. 1824 (Box 20, Folder 246)
    - Jacob, Stephen. 1778 (Box 20, Folder 246)
    - James, Lorenzo. 1825 (Box 20, Folder 246)
    - Jarvis, Samuel Farmer. 1805 (Box 20, Folder 246)
    - Johnson, Edward Whiting. 1869p (Box 20, Folder 246)
    - Jones, Isaac. 1742 (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - Jones, Isaac. 1757 (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - Jones, Isaac. 1792 (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - Jones, Samuel Beach. 1831 (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - Jones, William Hemphill. 1831 (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - Kanouse, Peter. 1831h (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - Keteltas, Philp Doddridge. 1792 (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - Lamb, Joseph. 1717 (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - Lamont, George Darwin. 1840 (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - Landon, Jonathan. 1763 (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - Langdon, John. 1809 (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - Lanman, James. 1788 (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - Lawrence, Edward Ashton. 1884 (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - Lounsbury, John. 1837m (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - Lyman General Folder. 1738-1783 (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - Lyman, Sidney Haskell. 1839m (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - Lynde, William Pitt. 1838 (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - McDermott, Charles. 1828 (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - Magill, Seagrove William. 1831 (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - Marsh, Joseph Whiting. 1763 (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - Mather General Folder. 1705-1829 (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - Mills, Charles Spotswood. 1833 (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - Minor, Israel. 1862 (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - Morris, Dewitt Clinton. 1840 (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - Morse, Sidney Edwards. 1811 (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - Nash, David Hull. 1834m (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - New, Erastus. 1863 (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - Newell, Abel. 1751 (Box 21, Folder 251)
    - Osborn, Norris Galpin. 1880 (Box 21, Folder 251)
    - Osborne, Daniel. 1763 (Box 21, Folder 251)
    - Osgood, Jonathan. 1789 (Box 21, Folder 251)
    - Pardee, Amos. 1793 (Box 21, Folder 251)
    - Parker, Daniel. 1798 (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - Pearl, Joshua F., 1836 (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - Peet, Harvey Prindell. 1822 (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - Perkins, Alfred James. 1827 (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - Perry, Joshua. 1775 (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - Peters, George Absalom. 1881h (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - Pierce, Franklin Williams. 1876 (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - Plummer, George. 1804 (Box 21, Folder 253)
    - Pomeroy, Josiah. 1762 (Box 21, Folder 253)
    - Pomeroy, Josiah. 1770 (Box 21, Folder 253)
    - Pope, John. 1815 (Box 21, Folder 253)
    - Porter, Timothy. 1726 (Box 21, Folder 253)
    - Rogers, Ammi. 1790 (Box 21, Folder 253)
    - Sanford, Edward Isaac. 1847 (Box 21, Folder 253)
    - Sanford, Ezekiel. 1815 (Box 21, Folder 253)
    - Sheldon, Henry Kent. 1859 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Sherman, Josiah. 1765h (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Sholes, Charles Mather. 1882 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Silliman, Ebenezer. 1727 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Silliman, George Bliss. 1881 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Silliman, Gold Selleck. 1752 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Silliman, Gold Selleck. 1796 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Skinner, Aaron Nichols. 1823 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Smith, Abraham Miller. 1808 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Smith, William. 1719 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Smith, William. 1745 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Sneed, Samuel Kirby. 1820 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Spencer, Horatio Nelson. 1821 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Spencer, Israel Selden. 1857 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Stafford, Ward. 1812 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Staples, Job. 1808 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Staples, Sophos. 1809 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Stevens, John Austin. 1813 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Tallmadge, Benjamin. 1830h (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - Taylor, George. 1824m (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - Thomas, Robert S. 1844h (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - Thompson, James. 1789 (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - Tod, George. 1795 (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - Todd, Samuel. 1734 (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - Tomlinson, John Atwood. 1856h (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - Treat, Charles. 1722 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Tullar, Martin. 1777 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Tuttle, Moses. 1745 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Vaill, Herman Landon. 1824h (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Vanderburgh, Federal. 1826m (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Walton, John. 1720 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Washington, George. 1839 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Watkins, Hezekiah. 1859 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - Way, Francis Roscoe. 1860 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - Webster, Pelatiah. 1746 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - White, Ebenezer. 1733 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - White, Ebenezer Russell. 1760 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - White, Henry. 1821 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - White, John. 1774 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - White, Stephen. 1736 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - Whittelsey General Folder (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Wickes, Thomas Scudder. 1847 (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Wilcoxson, Martin Van Buren. 1847 (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Williams General Folder (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Williams, Timothy. 1785 (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Williamson, Lewis Pugh. 1821 (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Winchester, George. 1816 (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Woodruff, Samuel. 1782 (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Wooster, David. 1738 (Box 21, Folder 259)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence about Yale graduates
    - A General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 260)
    - B General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 260)
    - Boltwood, Lucius M., 1863-1894, undated (Box 22, Folder 260)
    - C General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 260)
    - D General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 261)
    - E-F General.., 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 261)
    - G General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 262)
    - Gleason, Elon, 1850-1870, undated (Box 22, Folder 262)
    - H General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 262)
    - I-K General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 263)
    - L General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 263)
    - M-O General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 263)
    - P-Q General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 264)
    - R General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 264)
    - S General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 264)
    - Starr, Frank Farnsworth, 1878-1912 (Box 22, Folder 265)
    - T General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 265)
    - W General, 1835-1912, undated (Box 22, Folder 265)
- Subject Files, Circa 1860-1920; Series II; 1' 8" (4 boxes)
  - Correspondence, 1861-1920, undated (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Packard, Prof. L.R., 1866-1884 (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
  - Writings and Lectures
    - "Ezra Stiles and his Diary", 1884 November (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - "History in Names", 1889 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Introduction to volume on local names, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Jonathan Edwards, 1903 October (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Research notes
    - Age in Yale College, 1894-1896, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Ages of deceased Yale presidents and professors: list, Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - "Ancient Commencement Theses of Yale College", Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Chronology of Yale history; note book, some notes laid in, Undated (Box 27)
    - Clap, Thomas, Undated (Box 27)
      See also: box 23, folder 14
    - Connecticut topics, Undated (Box 27)
    - Cutler, Rector, Undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Davenport, John, Undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Distribution of emigrants in New England by counties of Old England, Undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Early fellows of Yale College, 1875-1895, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - English University men in the U.S., 1879-1880, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Harvard topics, Undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - "New Haven Printers Employed on College Publications," list, Undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - "Oldest Surviving Graduates of Yale College," queries about Yale history, 1882-1890 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Regicides: Dixwell, Whalley and Goffe, 1873-1900, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Slang Dictionary, "Sparsa Coëgi," notebook, Undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Social distinctions in College: includes correspondence, 1893-1894, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Social distinctions in College: lists, Undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - "Succession of Yale Fellows," list, Undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - "Textbooks and authors used in Yale College in the 18th Century," typescript, Undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - "Tuition and Roomrent," Yale College, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Williams, Rector, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Yale, Elihu, Bishop Berkeley, Rector Clap, David Yale, booklet, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Yale topics, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified material, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Volumes